CHRISTINA XAMIN

CONTACT

cxamin@gmail.com



(416)-523-3132



www.christinaxamin.com

1547 Mississauga Valley Blvd Mississauga, ON, Canada L5A 3X8

SKILLS

- Proficient in Adobe Creative Suite
- Confident working with both Macs and PCs, as well as their accompanying software (Microsoft Office, iWork, etc.)
- Understanding of HTML, CSS, and JavaScript
- Excels in use of social media outlets (including Twitter, Instagram, Facebook, YouTube. Pinterest and Tumblr)
- Ability to work in a team with a wide range of people
- · Able to make decisions and work through problems
- Manages time effectively
- Easily adapts to new situations
- Presents ideas and opinions in an open and unbiased way

CERTIFICATIONS

CPR Level C + AED

Ambitious designer with 5+ years experience in a professional design environment and a Bachelor of Interaction Design degree. Highly proficient in graphic design, video editing and web design software. Background in visual and creative arts using both traditional and digital elements.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Interaction Design Sheridan College

September 2014 - April 2018

Visual and Creative Arts Advanced Diploma Sheridan College

January 2012 - May 2014

EXPERIENCE

MARKETING ADMINISTRATOR Crafted Décor, Mississauga, ON

October 2017- May 2018

- Managed company's web and social media presence by creating content and engaging with followers
- Developed newsletters and gift guides that highlighted current products to promote sales

INTERACTIVE AND TECHNICAL MEDIA WRITER INTERN Rapid7, Toronto, ON

May 2017- September 2017

- Guided users through UI by contributing to company's software help documentation
- Collaborated with multiple teams to create documents that outlined in-product features

GRAPHIC DESIGN ASSISTANT (CONTRACT) Oakville Public Library, Oakville, ON

May 2016- August 2016

- · Created various promotional material for print, web and environmental applications
- · Maintained a graphic consistency by adhering to the library's visual identity and AODA compliancy
- Provided branding and graphic support for the 2016 TD Summer Reading Program